Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Deputy Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the deputy dean, 1953-1989; Accession 1990-A-059
  - Graduate Students/Assistants in Research on Medical School Grants, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Patient Matters (GTC), 1974-1984 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Profile of Grant/Contact Support and Administration, Yale Univ. SOM, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Office for Women in Medicine to 1986 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Office for Women (R. Codish), 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Chairmen's Lunch, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - University Council Committee, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Meeting of 1980 Feb 21, 22 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Meeting of 1979 Feb 8, 9 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Meeting of 1978 Mar 29, 30 (postponed from Feb 9, 10) (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Meeting of 1977 Apr 21, 22 (postponed from Feb 10, 11) (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Meeting of 1976 Oct 14, 15 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Meeting of 1976 Jun 3, 4 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - University Council Report on the Committee on Medical Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Ranks and Titles, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Part-time Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Chairman's Mini-Retreat, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Disaster Plan, 1968-1979 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Surgery Search, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Dr. Brennan Visit, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Surgery Search Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Office for Women Search, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Office for Women - 1986 Search Expenses (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Office for Women - Search for Director, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Anesthesiology Search Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Affirmative Action Committee
  - Associate Health Practitioner Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Chairman's Meetings (Committees)
    - 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Ad Hoc Committees on Computers in Medicine, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Computers in Medicine Committees, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Planning and Priorities, Joint Committee
    - 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Committee on Tenure
    - 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Committee on Tenure, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Committee on Tenure, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Committee on Tenure - P and P Committee Members, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Postdoctoral Education, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Yale - New Haven Hospital Committee 150th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 217)
- Records of the deputy dean, Richard Belitsky, 1984-2005; Accession 2015-A-007
  Restricted until January 1, 2040
  - Preparing Physicians for the Future: A Program in Medical Education, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Proposal for offering medical student research fellowships in basic sciences, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proposal for the Robert Wood Johnson clinical scholars program, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Special Medical Education Committee, 1987-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Task force for curriculum evaluation, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)